http://www.museknowledge.com/privacy-policy/

Login
About UsWho We AreWhat We DoOur HistoryNewsOur SolutionsOur ProductsMuse Knowledge SearchMuse Knowledge HybridMuse Knowledge ProxyMuse Knowledge HarvestOur ProcessGet StartedOur AllianceAlliance PartnersLocationsCustomer Stories
About UsWho We AreWhat We DoOur HistoryNewsOur SolutionsOur ProductsMuse Knowledge SearchMuse Knowledge HybridMuse Knowledge ProxyMuse Knowledge HarvestOur ProcessGet StartedOur AllianceAlliance PartnersLocationsCustomer StoriesNewsContact UsLogin
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
When you are using our website or our products we may collect at certain stages both anonymous and personal identifiable information.
Personal Information
We only collect personal information if it is mandatory for a certain process and we collect the minimum information for the process to work and provide you the best experience. We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, request a trial or fill out a form. As appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail, name or company name and address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Anonymous information
Like most website operators, we collect non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, IP address and the date and time of each visitor request. The purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use our website. For aggregating statistical data for our own use, we are employing the Google Analytics and Google AdWords Tracking tools. Google’s Privacy Policy may be found here: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. Note that we are not making any of these aggregated statistics public.
When you request technical support assistance for our products, in case you encounter a certain issue, we may need information on the actions that you have taken in using our products and eventually the corresponding product log files in order to assist you.  Any information that you may provide to us of this nature is being provided by you only with your consent.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website and products We continually strive to improve our website offerings and our products based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To improve customer service Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To send periodic e-mails The e-mail address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates related to the products and services that you have expressed interest in, requested trials for and also information on new related products developed or licensed by Muse Knowledge.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each e-mail.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except for the purpose of helping us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still request information or assistance by contacting our Customer Service team.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing services to you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or other’s rights, property, or safety.
EU General Data Protection Regulation Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the European Union General Data Protection Regulations– link to https://www.eugdpr.org(EUGDPR). We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of the USA COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act – link to https://www.ftc.gov/enforcement/rules/rulemaking-regulatory-reform-proceedings/childrens-online-privacy-protection-rule - and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and our products and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms and Conditions of Use.
Your Consent
By using our site or our products you consent to our online Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 20th February 2018.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.
Muse Knowledge Headquarters
CaleaBucuresti, Bl. 27B, Sc. 1, Ap. 10 Craiova, 200675, ROMANIA
Muse Knowledge SearchMuse Knowledge HybridMuse Knowledge ProxyMuse Knowledge Harvest
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
